

Computer Science student · Double degree in Business Administration

□ (+33) 6-49-11-53-54 | ■ hugo.mathh@gmail.com | ♠ hugomath.com | • Mathugo | • Industrial hugo-mathh | • Description | • Des

# Summary.

Hello! I'm a final-year student in computer engineering with a double degree in business administration.

I am excited by AI, in particular neural networks, embedded machine learning, federated learning and its commercial applications. I have also worked as a freelancer in software development and AI since 2019. See my website See my website to know me better!

# **Work Experience**

Edge AI Engineer France, Lanr

ORANGE LABS - INTERNSHIP - INDUSTRY 4.0 - COMPUTER VISION AND EDGE AI

April. 2022 - August 2022

- Train and evaluate SOTA computer vision models on custom datasets using **Federated Learning (Flower, MobileNetv2-SSD, Custom CNN)**
- Local models evaluation on clients and then aggregating the weights on a remote server. Models monitoring with MLFlow. Deployment on embedded devices (Jetson Xavier, TX2, PI3, Coral) with quantized models (Tflite, Pytorch Docker) Check this repo!
- Design a complete Robotic solution for the 4.0 Industry. Grab objects by estimating 3D coordinates using depth camera, AI models and a roboting arm. App fully containerized with Docker, results on MQTT and FastAPI (Yolov5, Opencv, Pytorch, RestAPI, Docker) Check this repo

**Dev Full Stack - Freelance**Switzerland, Milvigne

ATHENAIS SA - SEMICONDUCTOR FAULT DETECTION - FREELANCE IN A STARTUP

April. 2020 - Now

- This experience allowed me to improve my coding skills (C#, Python, .NET, Angular) as well as my skills in Computer vision and Data science
- Working remotely in a startup environment enabled me complete autonomy and decision-making over software development.
- Taking agile decisions and implementations to make the client satisfied was one of the big challenges that we faced.
- The project was about coding an optical wafer inspection software for the industry in a Swiss startup (fault detection) .NET Python C++

## **Education**

ESIREM Dijon, France

ENGINEERING DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - SPECIALIZED IN SOFTWARE AND KNOWLEDGE ENGINEERING

2018 - 2023

- · Software engineering, Neural Networks, Image processing, Data science, Big Data, Parallel Computing, Electronics, Networks
- · Mathematics (linear algebra, analysis, statistics), Physics (waves, signal processing, quantum physics, optics, line transmission)

IAE Dijon Dijon, France

MASTER IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION - DOUBLE DEGREE

Dijon, manec

· Company Management, Human Resources, Finance, Evaluation of costs and creation of a company, Strategic Marketing analysis

#### **Chalmers University of Technology**

Götebora Sweder

MASTER 1 ERASMUS STUDENT

August 2021 - January 2022

- Neural Network GPA: 4 (US) 21/24 Mobile Computing GPA: 4 (US) 130.00/160.00 Data Science and AI Technology and Society
  - Al Federated Learning, Computer Vision Models, Edge Al, RNN, Transformers, Residual Networks, SVM, PCA, Clustering

**Programming** Python, C#, C++, C, .NET, WPF, XAML, Angular, Django, FastAPI, Rest API, Flutter, Numpy, Java, Electron

Software Pytorch, Tf, MLFlow, Docker, Kubernetes, VMWare, OpenCV, UNIX, Github, GCP, Firebase, PostgreSQL, NoSQL

**Soft skills** Entrepreneurship, eager to learn, project management, Agile integration, open-minded, sociable, professional english

### **Honors & Awards**

### PROGRAMMING

2021 **Finalist**, Datathon of Burgundy - Auto-segmentation of Cardiac MRI Dijon, Franc

2019 **First prize**, Webcup - programming competition. This lasted 24 hours and the framework used was Angular

Diion France

### **ENTREPRENEURSHIP**

2021 **Finalist, Finance for Good**. 5 month business creation program. See: **deepwallet**Paris, France

2021 **Finalist, Les Entrep'**. 6 month business creation program as a project manager.

Dijon, France

#### **CERTIFICATION**

Les Entrep', Conduct an entrepreneurship project, work in team, establish costs, create the business
CCNA1, Cisco certification - Basic understanding of networks
Dijon, France
Dijon, France

2021 **PEPITE**, National student entrepreneur status

iion Franc